A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, President, Joshua Lederberg FA1118
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, President, Joshua Lederberg
1978-1989
Rockefeller Archive Center
Lederberg, Joshua
Rockefeller University.
FA1118
0.44 document box(es)
1 document box.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 305
Arrangement
As received.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: biographical material, clippings, photographs, programs, memoranda, and correspondence.
- Biographies, RU, Public Information Office (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Clippings (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Installation, 1978 October 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Photographs (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Memoranda re: Administration, 1978 November 16 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- "A Celebration of 40 years of Bacterial Conjugation - 35 Years of Bacterial Transduction" - printed programs, 1986 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Japan Trip 1984: Directory of RU Alumni in Japan (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Articles (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Genetic Recombination in Bacteria: A Discovery Account", American Review of Genetics, 21:23-46, 1987
  - "Gene Recombination and Linked Segregations in Escherichia coli", in Perspectives, Anectdotal, Historical, and Critical Commentaries on Genetics, eds, James F. Crow and William F. Dove, Genetics Society of America, Genetics, 117:1-4.
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)